# { Matheus Seabra }

# >>> SOFTWARE ENGINEER



#### PERSONAL SUMMARY

I'm a full-stack software engineer with over 5 years building web and mobile applications from client to server. Over the years I had the privilege of working with spectacular agile software engineering teams in industries ranging from Edtech, Fintech and Enterprise.

## GET IN TOUCH

Portfolio: matheuseabra.me

Github: <u>github.com/matheuseabra</u>

Email: matheus vieira coelho@gmail.com

Phone: +55 27 99284-3758

Vitória ES - Brazil

# TECHNOLOGIES & TOOLS

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JavaScript
- · React, Vue.js
- React Native
- Node.js
- Python
- GraphQL
- PostgresSQL
- MongoDB
- Redis
- JWT, Auth0
- Docker
- Linux
- Amazon Web Services
- CircleCI
- Git
- GitHub

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Software Engineer**

FineTune Learning | 2019 - Present

Working with the innovation team, collaborating with PO's, Designers and QA engineers helping to deliver the vision for their main product FineTune Writing, scaling the product up to thousands of students in the U.S.

#### Frontend Developer

Vibe | 2018 - 2019

Responsible for defining the overall client-side architecture for the applications projects and mentoring junior developers to use the appropriate design patterns, development practices and processes. The team was able to deliver features faster due to the processes applied.

#### Frontend Developer

Acception | 2017 - 2018

Led a successful refactor of the UI layout and client-side legacy architecture from jQuery to a modern frontend architecture built with React. Clients were delighted with the end result.

## **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

#### Rocketseat

GoStack Bootcamp | 2020

#### **Treehouse**

Fullstack JavaScript Development | 2017

#### Federal University of Pará

BS Information Systems | 2013 - 2017